他们需要我们的帮助
They need our help.
你必须留在这里
You are staying here.
该死  玛姬  我们走
Damn it, Maggie, let's go!
先做个了结
Not until it's done.
住手  不然她就死了
Stop! Or she's dead.
把枪和刀子扔在地上
Guns, knives on the ground right now.
外套不错
Nice jacket.
对一个凶残的婊子来说
For a murderous bitch.
我们先把她衣服脱了  再开枪打死她
Well, we'll take it off her before we shoot her.
包扎的不对  我能感受到  没有止住
It ain't on there right, I can feel it. It ain't stopping.
我会弄紧的  天啊  给我点时间
I'm getting it tighter. Jesus, give me a second.
该死  你切断了我的血液循环
Son of a bitch, you're cutting off my circulation.
小伙子  本来就该这样
Well, sport, it's supposed to.
那是什么
Hell was that?
是普里莫
It's Primo.
该死  他们抓到了他  给我对讲机
Damn it, they've got him. Give me the walkie.
亲爱的  发生了什么
Babe, what's happening?
放下枪  混蛋
Lower your gun, prick.
拿着柯尔特蟒蛇左轮的那个
You, with the colt python.
你们所有人放下武器
All of you, lower your weapons right now.
出来吧  我们谈谈
Come on out. Let's talk.
有多少人
How many we got?
看到八个
Eight in sight.
太多了
Too many.
不  我们能干掉他们  我们杀过更多人
No, we can take 'em. We took more.
我们不会出去  但我们会谈谈
We're not coming out, but we will talk.
名字
Names.
Names!
我是玛姬  她是卡萝尔
I'm Maggie, she's Carol.
卡萝尔和玛姬在我们手上
We've got a Carol and a Maggie.
我想你们应该想谈谈这个
I'm thinking that's something you want to chat about.
我们现在就解决这事
Now, we're gonna work this out right now,
而且要按我们的方法
And it's going to go our way.
你可以看见我们也抓了你们的人
You can see we have one of yours.
我们来交易
We'll trade.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
首先我想跟玛姬和卡萝尔讲话
First I want to talk to maggie and carol,
确保她们没事
make sure they're all right.
我来让你们通话  说自己没事
I'm gonna put you on. You say you're fine.
如果你们想耍花招  我会知道的
I'll know if you try anything else.
瑞克  我是卡萝尔
Rick, it's Carol.
-我没事  但  -该你了
- I'm-- I'm fine, but-- - - Now you.
瑞克  我是玛姬  我们都没事
Rick, it's Maggie. We're both okay.
-我们会搞定的  -闭嘴
- We'll figure thi-- - Shut up.
现在你信了  来谈吧
You have your proof. Let's talk.
好  我们现在就交易
This is the deal right here.
放走她们  你们可以得到自己的人并活下去
Let 'em go, you can have your guy back and live.
两个换一个  不公平啊
Two for one, that's not much of a trade.
你们别无选择
You don't have another choice
不然你们早就行动了
or you would've done something about it already.
我们得救他回来
We have to get him back.
普里莫能照顾好自己
Primo can take care of himself.
他能给我包扎伤口
He can patch me up.
我需要他  拜这个婊子所赐
I need him, thanks to that bitch.
你胆子哪去了  宝拉
You lost your balls, Paula.
你应该一枪爆了她的头
You should've shot her in the head
这样他们就能听见她死了
so they could hear her die.
你能不能把嘴闭上  我会解决这个的
If you could just shut up, I'll solve this.
要么答应交易  要么冲进去
Then make the deal or we go in.
她说了闭嘴  你就把嘴闭上
She said shut up, so shut it.
你应该庆幸她没有睾丸
You should be glad she doesn't have
不会被绊倒
a sack of gonads to trip over.
我知道你们在商量
Look, I know you're talking it over.
这个交易很公平
It's a fair trade.
出来吧  我们换人
Just come out, we do this,
然后大家都能离开
we all walk away.
自作聪明的混蛋
Smug prick.
他一定觉得我们是傻子
He must think we're stupid.
这是件好事
That's a good thing.
成交吗
Do we have a deal?
我一会儿再和你联系
I'll get back to you.
《行尸走肉》
前进
Move!
转弯
Turn.
等着
Wait.
欧米伽  救世军伤亡
Omega, Omega, Saviors down.
转到伽马  代号"火"
Go to Gamma, code "Fire."
阿尔法频道不安全  我们按规定来
Alpha channel is not clear. We follow the protocol.
你们死哪里去了
Where the hell are you guys?
在西边...
Out west of the--
15英里...
15 mi-- on-- way.
我们正在前往断点
We're headed to the break point.
转到西塔频道  代号不变
Switch to Theta channel, same code.
假如我没到  切换到阿尔法  进行监听
If I'm not there, toggle to Alpha, listen in.
收到
Copy that.
我讨厌这个鬼地方
I hate this damn place.
安全屋
Safe house.
(屠宰间  生肉处理)
这地方没什么安全可言
There ain't nothing safe about it.
这地方会救我们一命的
This place is gonna save our asses.
坐地上去
Get on the ground.
你  这边
You there.
你  那边
You, over there.
你们一定在想有没有办法脱身
You're wondering if there's a way out of this.
没有  除非我开口
There isn't. Not unless I say so.
宝拉  我需要支援
Paula, I need backup!
我想马上就杀了你俩
I want to kill you both right now.
我好不容易才忍住不下手
It's taking all I have not to,
所以你们敢动动心思试试
so go ahead, I dare you, try something. Just see what happens.
上一次来人检查这里是什么时候
When's the last time anyone checked this place?
一个月前这里还是好的
It was fine a month ago.
甜心  那可是一个月前啊
Sweetie, that was a month ago.
情况变坏得很快的
Shit hards quick.
枪没了  食物也没了
The guns have gone bye-bye, the food's gone bye-bye,
过道里前前后后都是行尸
And we got growlers up and down the halls.
说明人也可以穿过去
Means people can get through, too.
-也许我们该走了  -卡萝尔
- Maybe we should get gone. - Carol!
-是吗  去哪里  -哪里也不去
- Yeah? Where the hell to? - Nowhere.
过道里有行尸  正好是免费保安
Got dead in the halls? Free security.
如果那些混蛋比我们的人先到这里
Those assholes get here before our people,
那些行尸能帮我们拖延一点时间
the cold bloods will buy us some time.
闭嘴
Shut up.
天啊  还在流血  应该止住了才对
Jesus, it's bleeding. It's not supposed to keep bleeding.
-老莫  把绳子给我  -我不能死
- Molly, give me the rope. - I'm not losing it.
-我不能  -你撑着点  天啊  唐尼
- I'm not. - So you grind it out. Jesus, Donnie.
去你的  雪儿  得把他换回来
Screw you, 'chelle! We have to get him back.
他能包扎好
He can fix it.
-我们必须这么做  宝拉  -不
- We have to, Paula. - No.
我看到他们了  而你没有
I saw them, you didn't.
他们占领了那里
They took the place down,
还拿了枪  他们会杀了我们的
They got the guns, they'll kill us, too.
我不会轻易认命
I'm not going down like that,
毕竟都撑到现在了
Not after making it this far.
怎么了
What?
她喘不上气了  快把她的口松开
She's hyperventilating. Somebody needs to take her gag off.
她真是个胆小鬼  不是吗
She's a nervous little bird, ain't she?
看看你
Look at you.
你这婊子是怎么活到现在的
Bitch, how did you make it this far?
亲爱的  你现在要深呼吸  冷静下来
Honey, you need to take some yoga breaths and calm your ass down.
我不能
I can't--
你是那种人啊
You're one of those.
你到底在怕什么
What are you so afraid of?
你真的怕死吗
Are you actually afraid to die?
事到如今  你还怕吃枪子儿不成
All this and you're scared of getting your ticket punched.
我是死是活不要紧
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
请别伤害玛姬
Just don't hurt Maggie.
别伤害孩子
Don't hurt the baby.
没错
Yeah, right.
她是怀孕了  但看着不像
She got a bun in the oven, she doesn't look it.
应该才两个月
I'm only two months, I think.
你也真是蠢
You're some kind of stupid,
这年头还被人搞大肚子
Getting knocked up at a time like this.
你觉得好笑吗
You think that's funny?
那什么时候怀孕不算蠢呢
When was it ever smart to get knocked up?
以前的女人还难产致死
Women used to just die in childbirth.
她们总觉得世界要毁灭了
And they always thought the world was gonna end.
再怎样都要挺过去  干嘛放弃
Living through it, why would you just give up?
但你真觉得你会挺过去吗
But are you gonna live through it?
真是可爱
Anyway, that's cute.
孩子才是重点
Babies are the point.
孩子是我们的未来
Children are our future.
给行尸当小点心还差不多
Making bite-size snacks for the dead.
重点是有口气站着
The point is to stay standing.
不
No.
行尸也能站着
Walkers do that.
我做出了自己的选择
I'm choosing something.
没错
That's right.
你选了
You are.
也做了
You did.
孩子
The baby.
亲爱的  你还没弄明白吧
Honey, in case you haven't noticed,
你遇到的问题比二手烟大得多
You've got bigger problems than a little secondhand smoke.
老莫
Molls.
你们比一群福音派的
Y'all are worse than a bunch
二年级小学生还让人头疼
of evangelical second graders.
那东西会害死你的
Those things'll kill you.
我已经要被害死了
They already have.
我只是活死人罢了
I'm a dead woman walking.
这意味着我们是同一条船上的
which puts us in exactly the same boat.
我的手臂好疼
My arm feels like it's on fire.
你把那个扯掉
You pull that off,
伤口就会像水龙头一样血流如注
you gonna be nothing but a spigot.
好了  坚持住
Okay, hold on.
侦察队马上就来  最多等半小时
Scout crew is coming. They're 30 minutes out, maybe less.
他等不了半小时了
He doesn't have 30 minutes.
他的神经要坏死了
His nerves are dying.
如果没有救治  他就会失去一只手
If he doesn't get medical help, he's gonna lose his arm,
甚至丢了性命
maybe his life.
我虽然不是医生  但我爸失去了一条腿
I'm not a doctor, but my dad lost his leg,
我至少知道这点
and I know that much.
你们的人  普里莫  你认为他能帮你吗
Your man, Primo, you think he can help you?
该结束这一切了
It's time to end this.
联系瑞克吧
Talk to Rick.
等半小时
30 minutes.
你知道我有什么不满吗
You know my problem?
是她把我打成这样的
She did this to me.
她一手造成的  现在却坐在那
She did it and she's just sitting there
-安然无恙  毫发无伤  -T
- right as rain, fully intact. - T
不  不要交换人质了
No, you're not gonna make the trade.
我们现在就把她们杀了
And we just do 'em both now.
不行  我们要等其他人
No, we wait for the others.
我们不能犯傻  我们需要有保险措施
We have to be smart. We need insurance.
-那就对她的胳膊也开一枪  -不行
- Then shoot her in the arm, too.- No.
你真要护着这个胆小的贱人  而不顾我吗
You really gonna stick up for some gutless bitch over me?
-该死  -闭嘴
- God damn it! - Shut up.
别逼我  宝拉
Don't push me, Paula.
闭嘴
Shut up!
别碰她
Leave her alone!
不  不要
No! No!
你这愚蠢  嚣张的贱人
You dumb, uppity bitch!
你确实挺蠢的
You really are some kind of stupid.
把她带出去  看她是否知道些什么
Take her out. See if she knows anything.
之前就该这么做的
Should've done that before.
走
Move.
你有不错的衣服
You got nice clothes,
有时间造人
time to make babies.
你们躲在一个生活条件不错的地方
You're holed up somewhere good.
告诉我在哪
Tell me where.
别拖时间了  贱人
Don't draw this out, bitch.
告诉我在哪
Just tell me where.
就当帮帮你自己  和你肚子里的孩子
Help yourself and the baby in your belly.
想活命  就得给我们带来好处
The way you stay alive is you produce for us.
你们并不是好人
You're not the good guys.
你应该知道这一点
You should know that.
他打得真狠  孩子
He got you good, kid.
他处于疼痛中
He's in pain.
男人耐痛能力差
Guys can't handle pain.
打扰下
Excuse me?
我只是想道句谢
Just wanted to say thank you
感谢你们帮了玛姬和我
for helping Maggie, for helping me.
-我丈夫艾迪  他以前常常...  -是吗
- My husband Ed, he used to... - Yeah?
我不关心你丈夫以前是否虐待过你
I don't care if your old man used to ring your bell.
我很清楚你是什么样的人  卡萝尔
I see exactly who you are, Carol.
我知道
I know.
你很可悲
You're pathetic.
你想觉得我们是一类人
You wanna think we're just the same?
尽管这么想好了
Go ahead.
你错了
You're wrong.
他只是个给我暖床的罢了
He's just a warm body for my bed.
仅此而已  我可以在他睡梦中杀了他
That's it. I could kill him in his sleep.
你真的信那个鬼东西吗
Do you really believe in that crap?
我的信仰帮我度过了丧女之痛
My faith got me through the death of my daughter.
好消息是也许很快你又能见到她了
Well, the good news is maybe you'll see her again soon.
你的手怎么了
What happened?
偷东西  被抓了
I stole something. Got caught.
偷什么
What?
汽油  就从这里偷的
Gas, from this place.
-为什么  -为了找一辆新车
- Why? - To get a new car.
去找我男朋友的尸体
Look for my boyfriend's body.
你找到了吗
Did you find him?
他被炸死了
He was blown up.
没剩下什么了
Not much to find.
弗兰克
"Frankie."
-是他的名字吗  -当然不是
- Was that his name? - Hell, no.
我几乎不了解他
I barely knew him.
他是个混蛋
He was a dick.
弗兰克是我父亲
Frank was my dad.
我也曾想给我孩子取这个名字
And that's what I was gonna name the baby.
-我很遗憾  -不
- I'm sorry. - No.
你才不遗憾
You aren't.
我今天不想死
I'm not planning to die today.
是啊  我也不想
Yeah, me neither.
问题是  我们中有一个人错了
Thing is, one of us is wrong.
告诉我在哪
Just tell me where.
你想过了吗
Have you thought about it?
回话
Talk to me.
你之前没好好听
You weren't listening.
我说我会联系你的
I said I'd contact you.
如果我说我很抱歉  事情会有转机吗
Would it make a difference if I said I was sorry about that?
你有什么想法
What do you think?
我认为我们可以交换人质
I think we're gonna make the trade,
告诉我地点
so tell me where.
我们还没有同意
We haven't agreed to that.
你们会的
You will.
知道吗  我可不敢保证
You know what? I'm not so sure.
大部分的风险都在我们这边
We'd be taking most of the risk,
却得不到太多的回报
not getting much in the way of a reward.
另一个选择对你们而言是行不通的
The other option won't work out for you.
我们愿意冒险一试
We'll take our chances.
你们不用这样的
You don't have to do this.
你们不用抗争的
You don't have to fight.
你们的人杀了我们所有人
Your people killed all of my people.
我们当然要抗争
Of course we gotta fight.
-我们不想的  -但你们做了
- We didn't want to. - But you did.
告诉我原因
So tell me why.
你们的人在公路上伏击我们的人
Your people ambushed my people on the road,
想抢走我们的一切东西
tried to take everything we had.
他们想杀了我们的人
They were gonna kill them.
该死
Well, damn.
现在我们知道T的小队出了什么事了
So now we know what happened to T's group.
那群白痴
Those idiots.
-当时估计很招摇  -好吧
- Probably put on a big show. - Okay,
合情合理
fair play.
你们是正当防卫
You were just defending yourselves.
但是
But, see,
你们的人在公路上杀了他们
your people killed them on the road, right?
把他们炸成碎片了
Blew them to pieces.
为什么还不停手
So, why not stop?
他们说他们是尼根的手下
They said they were working for Negan.
你对尼根了解些什么
And what do you think you know about Negan?
他听起来像个疯子
He sounded like a maniac.
我们都很害怕  觉得有必要阻止他
We were scared. We had to stop him.
亲爱的  亲爱的
Sweetie, sweetie.
我们都是尼根
We are all Negan.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
能给我来根吗
Can I have one?
看看你  胆小鬼
Well, look at you, little bird.
我以为你不赞同抽烟呢
I didn't think you approved.
我是不赞同
I don't.
你确实很弱
You are weak.
你到底在怕什么
What are you so afraid of?
怕到都无法坚守自己的原则了
So scared, you can't even stick to your own principles.
你不会想让我坚守我的原则的
You don't want me to stick to my own principles.
我之前是个秘书
I was a secretary before.
给老板端咖啡
I fetched coffee for my boss
让他自我感觉良好
and made him feel good about himself.
我大多数时间
I spent most of my days reading
都在读弱智的励志邮件
stupid inspirational e-mails
试图让自己感觉好点
to try and feel good about myself.
有这么一个流传很广的邮件
There was this one that kept going around.
一个年轻的女人遇到了困难
A young woman was having a hard time
跟她妈妈说她想放弃
and told her mom she wanted to give up,
她妈妈走进了厨房
so her mom went to the kitchen
开始烧三壶水
and started boiling three pots of water.
一壶放了根胡萝卜  一壶放了颗鸡蛋
She put a carrot in one, an egg in another,
最后一壶放了咖啡豆
and ground coffee beans in the last one.
煮了一会后  她妈妈说
After they had boiled a while, her mom said,
"看  这三样东西都放水里煮过了
"Look, all three things went through the same boiling water.
萝卜放进去之前很硬  煮完后变软了
The carrot went in strong and came out soft.
鸡蛋本来很脆弱  但煮完后变硬了
The egg was fragile and came out hard.
然而咖啡豆却改变了水"
But the coffee beans changed the water itself."
你应该想成为咖啡豆
You're supposed to want to be the coffee beans.
但是  咖啡对我而言只是
See, to me, coffee was just a thing
我老板会喝光的东西
that my boss would drink up.
不管我给他续杯多少次
No matter how many times I refilled his damn cup,
他总是能喝完
it was just never enough.
军队接手华盛顿的时候我在上班
I was at work when the Army took over DC.
他们不准我们离开
We weren't allowed to leave.
他们首先得让所有重要人士撤离
They had to evacuate all the important people first--
国会成员  政府员工
members of Congress, government employees.
所以我和我的上司待在一起
So I was stuck with my boss.
而不是我的家人
Not my family--
我的丈夫  我的四个女儿
my husband, my four girls...
我的上司又笨又弱  他会死的
My boss was weak and stupid and he was going to die
还会拖累我
and he was going to take me down, too.
他是我杀的第一个人
He was the first person I killed
这样我才能活下来
so that I could live.
我杀了十几个人后就不数了
I stopped counting when I hit double digits.
从那以后我也没有愧疚感了
That's right around the time I stopped feeling bad about it.
我不像你
I am not like you.
我仍是我  但是更好的我
I'm still me, but better.
我抛弃了一切  这让我更强大
I lost everything and it made me stronger.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我还活着
I'm alive.
跟那些人  那些凶手一起
With those people, those killers.
你们的人也是凶手  卡萝尔
Your people are killers, Carol.
说明你也是一名凶手
That makes you a killer.
你...你才是
You-- you're the one.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你才是怕死的那个
You're the one who's afraid to die.
而且你还是会死的
And you're going to.
你会死的
You will die.
如果你不解决这件事  你就会死
It's what's gonna happen if you don't work this out.
你会杀了我吗
Are you going to kill me?
希望不会
I hope not.
混蛋  你在吗
Asshole, are you there?
我在
I'm here.
我们考虑过了  我们想交易
We've thought about it. We want to make the trade.
很好
That's good.
I-66公路外两英里的地方有一块空地
There's a large field with a sign that says "God is dead"
上面有个标识牌写着"上帝已死"
about two miles down I-66.
各个方向的视野都很开阔
Good visibility in all directions.
我们十分钟后在那里见怎么样
We'll meet you there. 10 minutes?
十分钟
10 minutes.
不对  这也太简单了
Mm-mm. Now, that was too easy.
也许他们只是太想把他们的人救回去
Maybe they're just itching to get their people back.
不  没有静电噪音  应该有噪音的
No, there was no static. There should've been static.
他们离这里很近  说不定已经到了
They're close. They're probably already here.
我们很小心  但还是会留下踪迹
We were careful, but there were tracks.
-肯定会有的  -不...
- There had to be. - No...
他们杀了家里的所有人  他们有武器
They killed everybody back home. They have the weapons.
他们很清楚自己在干什么
They know what they're doing.
他们可能想等我们一走出门
They're probably waiting to kill us
就杀了我们
as soon as we walk out those doors.
-换我们就会这么做  -不
- That's what we'd do. - No.
你得听我说  求你了
You have to listen to me, please.
瑞克是信守承诺的人
Rick is a man of his word.
他不会拿我和玛姬的生命冒险
He wouldn't put me and Maggie at risk to attack.
那他就和你们一样蠢
Then he's just as stupid as you are.
你什么时候到
What's your ETA?
还有几分钟
A few minutes away,
-但车子没油了  -我们有油
- but the car is running on fumes. - We have gas.
我们给你加满油  然后出发
We'll fill you up and then we move.
快到的时候呼叫我们
Radio when you're back in the perimeter.
收到
Copy that.
我们得准备好
We gotta get ready.
叫上雪儿  别让她陷入战斗
Pull 'Chelle out so she doesn't get stuck in a fight.
我们需要准备好随时出发
We have to be ready to move at any second.
那个姑娘怎么办
What about the girl?
先留在这
Leave her for now.
我们要离开这  就得轻装上阵
If we leave, we travel light.
如果那帮混蛋来了  就在门口干掉他们
And if the pricks are here, we pick 'em off at the door.
老莫  我们得把这条过道清空
Molls, we need this hall clear.
别着急  甜心
Just a sec, sugar.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
必须没事
I have to be.
他们散开了  但我觉得我们能溜出去
They've spread out, but I think we can make it past them.
-我们必须试一下  -我们不能留活口
- We have to try. - We can't leave them alive.
不  我们应该直接走
No, we should just go.
卡萝尔  我们得做个了结  必须这样
Carol, we have to finish this. We have to.
他已经死了
He was already dead.
-他要尸变了  -我们走吧
- He's turning. - We should go.
我们需要枪
We need a gun.
给我
Give me that.
吃屎去死吧  唐尼
Eat shit and die, Donnie!
你在哪呢  美女
Where are ya, Magnolia?
我要割开你那漂亮的...
I wanna bloody up that nice--
走吧
Let's go.
他们用行尸来防止我们逃跑
They're using them to keep us in,
阻拦其他人进来
keep the others out.
走吧
Come on.
我们得找到他们
We have to find 'em.
走吧
Just run.
打死她
Shoot her.
来吧  开枪
Go on, do it.
你杀了唐尼  你杀了莫莉
You've killed Donnie, you've killed Molly.
你的人毁了我的家
Your people have destroyed my home.
-离开这  -卡萝尔
- Get outta here. - Carol.
你根本不知道
You have no idea.
我做过什么
The things I've done,
我放弃了什么
what I've given up,
我不得不做了什么
what I had to do.
-走吧  -卡萝尔  打死她
- Just run. - Carol, shoot her.
开枪吧  我已经一无所有了
Go ahead. I've already lost everything.
宝拉
Paula?
莫莉
Molly?
你这个撒谎的贱人
You lying bitch!
我来吧
I'll do it.
厉害啊
You're good.
胆小鬼
Nervous little bird.
你曾经是那样的
You were her.
但你现在已经不是了  对吗
But not now, right?
我也是
Me, too.
我说过让你走
I told you to run.
既然你本事这么大
If you could do all this,
那你到底怕的是什么  卡萝尔
what were you so afraid of, Carol?
我怕这个
I was afraid of this.
宝拉  我们接近了
Paula, we're approaching the perimeter.
能进去吗
Are we a go?
收到了吗
Do you copy?
我们在屠宰间见
Meet us on the kill floor.
我觉得我可能杀了18个人
I think I might have killed 18 people.
20个人
20.
我也应该在树林里杀了唐尼
I should've killed Donnie, too, in the woods.
完全能打中  我故意打偏的
I had a clear shot. I didn't miss.
如果我杀了他  这一切就不会发生了
None of this would've happened if I had just killed him.
-别想了  -我停不下来
- Don't think about it. - I can't stop.
快结束了
We're almost done.
当心  地板很滑
Careful. The floor's slick.
你确定是这里吗
You sure this is it?
她说是屠宰间
She said kill floor.
这门锁住了
Hey, this one's locked.
怎么回事
What the hell?! Agh!
玛姬
Maggie.
你还好吗
You okay?
我们发现了你们的踪迹
We got your trail.
-你点火了吗  -是的
- You start a fire? - Yeah.
你还好吗
Hey, you good?
不好
No.
过来
Come here.
他们死了  抓我们的人都死了
They're dead. They're all dead, the ones that took us.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
你还好吗
Hey, are you okay?
我只是
I just...
我做不下去了
I can't anymore.
没事了
It's okay.
你的朋友们都死了
Your friends are dead.
没人来救你了
No one's coming for ya.
所以你最好开口吧
So you might as well talk.
烧死他吧
Let him burn.
我问你最后一次
I'm gonna ask you one last time...
摩托是哪来的
how'd you get the bike?
-是我们找到的  -放屁
- We found it. - Like hell you did.
是我们找到的
We found it.
尼根昨晚在那栋楼里吗
Was Negan in that building last night
还是说他在这里
or was he here?
都对
Both.
我就是尼根  蠢货
I'm Negan, shithead.
我们可以谈很多有趣的事
There's a whole world of fun that we can talk about,
那我们就谈谈吧
so let's have a chat.
很抱歉变成这样
I'm sorry it had to come to this.